virante.com 2017-01-21

# Hive Digital Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to Privacy…

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information privacy policy practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Hive Digital website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

**Quote and Contact Forms**

Your Name  
Company Name  
Email address  
Phone number  
Website URL  
(etc.)

**Google Analytics**

We may collect information about your computer, including your operating system and browser type, for system administration and in order to create reports. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

The only cookies in use on our site are for Google Analytics. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it.

Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site.

Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page.

Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit this [Google page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

**Crazy Egg**

Crazy Egg’s Analysis Service is a web analytics service that gives us data about where users are clicking on our site. You can visit their privacy policy at: https://www.crazyegg.com/privacy and their opt-out feature at: https://www.crazyegg.com/opt-out.

**HotJar**

Hotjar is a all-in-one Analysis and Feedback tool that reveals the online behaviour and feedback of a website’s visitors. By combining both A) Analysis and B) Feedback tools, Hotjar gives Hive Digital, Inc. the ‘big picture’ of how to improve our site experience and its performance.

You can read more about [_the way HotJar works to protect data and safety_](https://docs.hotjar.com/docs/data-safety-and-security) as well as view their own privacy policy [_here_](https://www.hotjar.com/privacy).

### The Way We Use Information:

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. For example, we may discover that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose or track anything that could be used to identify these individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us directly via phone or email. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-800-650-0820 or send us an email at info@Hive Digital.marketing
